todaytoptrends.com 2014-11-05

# Privacy Policy

**View our site’s Privacy Policy**

In case you need any more info or have any kind of queries about our privacy policy, you can always contact us through the web site.

At [www.todaytoptrends.com](http://www.todaytoptrends.com/), the solitude of our visitors is connected with extreme value to us. This privacy statement document describes the kinds of personal information is acquired and gathered by www.todaytoptrends.com and how it’s utilized.

**Cookies along with Web Beacons**

WWW.todaytoptrends.com does make use of cookies to keep details about visitor’s choices, record user-precise details about which page the visitor access or see, customize Web page material depending on visitor’s browser type or other details which the visitor posts through their browser.

**DART Cookie**

Google, as a 3rd party merchant, uses cookies to provide advertisements on www.todaytoptrends.com.

Google’s implement of the DART cookie allows it to provide ads for the users dependent on their browse to www.todaytoptrends.com and other sites on the web.

If you want to invalidate cookies, you might do so via your browser options. More comprehensive details about cookie management along with particular web browsers are available at the browsers’ respected websites.

**Log Documents**

Such as many other Internet sites, www.todaytoptrends.com utilizes log files. The details within the log files consists of web protocol, type associated with browser, Internet Service Company, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and amount of clicks to investigate traits, manage the website, track users movement close to the site, and collect market information. IP addresses along with other such details aren’t linked to any information that’s individually recognizable.
